<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Material Docs</title>
    <link>localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Material Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Installation Installing Hugo Hugo itself is just a single binary without dependencies on expensive runtimes like Ruby, Python or PHP and without dependencies on any databases. You just need to download the latest version. For more information read the official installation guides.
Let&amp;rsquo;s make sure Hugo is set up as expected. You should see a similar version number in your terminal:
hugo version # Hugo Static Site Generator v0.15 BuildDate: 2016-01-03T12:47:47+01:00  Installing Material Next, assuming you have Hugo up and running the hugo-material-docs theme can be installed with git:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding content</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/adding-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/adding-content/</guid>
      <description>Hello world Let&amp;rsquo;s create our first content file for your documentation. Open a terminal and add the following command for each new file you want to add. Replace &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt; with a general term that describes your document in detail.
hugo new &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename.md  Visitors of your website will find the final document under www.example.com/&amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename/.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s possible to have multiple content files in the same section I recommend to create at least one index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Errors</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/errors/</guid>
      <description>Errors This error section is stored in a separate file, errors.md. DocuAPI allows you to split the single page documentation in as many files as needed. Files are included in the default Hugo page order . One way of ordering the pages is by setting the page `weight` in the front matter. Pages with lower weight will be listed first. The Kittn API uses the following error codes:
   Error Code Meaning     400 Bad Request &amp;ndash; Your request sucks   401 Unauthorized &amp;ndash; Your API key is wrong   403 Forbidden &amp;ndash; The kitten requested is hidden for administrators only   404 Not Found &amp;ndash; The specified kitten could not be found   405 Method Not Allowed &amp;ndash; You tried to access a kitten with an invalid method   406 Not Acceptable &amp;ndash; You requested a format that isn&amp;rsquo;t json   410 Gone &amp;ndash; The kitten requested has been removed from our servers   418 I&amp;rsquo;m a teapot   429 Too Many Requests &amp;ndash; You&amp;rsquo;re requesting too many kittens!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Development and Design Guidebook</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a guidebook on how to make video games. The main idea behind this guidebook is to provide a framework for creating interactive ideas to those either completely new to game development or people lookgin to refine their development process. In this guidebook we use Godot, GIMP and LMMS primarily, but you could easily follow along with replacements that cover the same topic.
All of the software we use in this guidebook is open source and free of charge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>